kaizenet.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

### We respect your privacy

Kaizenet Ltd will respect your privacy and ensure that all sensitive and personal information provided to us is lawfully processed and held in accordance to the Data Protection Act 1998. Personal/sensitive information is deemed to be any information that identifies a living individual.

### We keep your information safe

Kaizenet Ltd will control the data you supply and we agree to collect and control this information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Kaizenet Ltd contact information can be found on the contact page of our website.

### How do we collect your information?

We collect information from you when you submit an enquiry, visit our site, call us for information and send us an email. We collect the following information:

  * Your name
  * Your email address
  * Your company name, address, and telephone number

### What do we do with your information?

We will only use the information you provide us with to:

  * Make improvements to our service
  * Action any requests you make
  * Supply you with requested information
  * Conduct market research

_Kaizenet Ltd will not sell or share your personal data with others._

### We keep your information up to date

Kaizenet Ltd endeavor to keep all personal information that they store up to date. We will amend any information we find to be inaccurate or are informed is inaccurate at our earliest convenience.

To ensure compliance with the data protection act 1998, Kaizenet Ltd are happy to supply you with any details they hold about you. There is a £10+VAT admin fee for requests of this information.

### We track your online activities

Kaizenet collect information from your visit to our site. This information is only used to track browsing patterns and cannot be used to identify you personally.
